[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Any sense on where we are after one week in terms of the takings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "You know, things are certainly moving forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Is this a force for good or a forceful continued concern as America moves now to legalizing marijuana?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "It's disastrous.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well I'll tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How many lives, percentage-wise do you think it destroys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I think it destroys thousands.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 76, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "But what are ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Obviously, a pretty damning verdict there from Howard Samuels, from your experience of law enforcement, what do you make of this move today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "And the front lines that I've been on are ones of law enforcement obviously.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard Samuels"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Colorado", "Colorado", "Colorado"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "CC", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "The challenge is how do we responsibly regulate marijuana as a legal product given the failures in the past?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "OK, on that very point, are you happy with the steps that Colorado, for example, reporting you have to be 21 or older, you can buy up to an ounce with a license on stores (inaudible) Colorado ID, people from outside Colorado can buy a quarter ounce, users can also share an ounce of cannabis with a friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Are you happy with that criteria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "``", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Taking away their job, including that, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "... (inaudible) it should not be arrest record for marijuana, but you don't legalize it and mass produce it, just like the ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "And if not, why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Too late.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "How's your skin doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, you see, I look a little bit -- I've been called all kinds of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "You have Jahi back with you, are you able to say where she is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "We're not able to disclose where she is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jahi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Why do you believe that they're wrong, that there is still hope and she may still be alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Because we believe that as long as her heart is still pumping, she's still alive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Are you seeing any signs of what you think could be evidence that she is alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Absolutely, she is moving a lot more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "CD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Do they have complete legal rights over her body now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, the situation is sort one in limbo because the coroner on one hand says she is dead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "But do you want from a legal point of view to have more physicians examine her to determine whether they agree with the original verdict that she is brain dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No, what we wanted to do was have her mother have the ability to make a choice as to whether or not her daughter would stay on or come off of the vent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Should that always be, do you think, a family's choice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "You feel that strongly, Omari?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Omari"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "How long will you as a family persevere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Right now we're just taking it one day at a time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Are you working on the theory that miracles happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Not so much -- I mean absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jahi"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "For those who do have meet her, have met her, what kind of girl is she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Jahi is a very sweet girl.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Arthur Caplan, we've discussed this before, has anything changed in your opinion of this case since we last talked about it given that there's now the movement in terms of the apparent legal position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Nothing's changed medically.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arthur Caplan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Has anybody to your knowledge recovered after being declared brain dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "You know, I checked this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "You know, Piers, I think from a human perspective it's heartbreaking and difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Why does it not exist elsewhere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Because there is -- and frankly, you know, I don't know much about the New Jersey law but when you have a situation when a child is dead, the responsibility is for the hospital and the parents to come to terms and understand that but there is no remedy here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Why should we be stopping this family from being in that position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "You know, I'll answer this way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "If we left it up to you and me grieving over our families, who's going to say give up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "There's another case in Texas which is fascinating on a different level.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Now, where do you sit with that, Arthur Caplan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well, for me, Texas legislature has no business intruding into this tragedy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arthur Caplan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "We also know that his older brother Johnny is here as well has got into UMass, why did this story touching out with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "It was a story of hope and opportunity in an area that doesn't have too many of them, areas that have, you know, high crime, high poverty, and I met these boys, they weren't waiting for someone to help them, they were doing it on their own.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "OK, George let me start with you because you've been offered a place at Yale, but brilliantly you have made your mind (inaudible) because you're still quite fancy (inaudible), is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Yes, that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Yale"], "PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 453, "question": "How do you feel about what has happened to you and to your brother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Definitely really exciting that we have come such a long way from, you know, poverty, single parent, and it's definitely really exciting for me to be accepted to, you know, Ivy college but as well as for my brother to attend, you know, a college already and, you know, it feels amazing to, you know, be in the right path and...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Do you feel, Johnny, that you are now living perhaps the American dream your parents wanted to live when they came here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I don't know if I can call it the American dream but we're getting closer to that I suppose because I have still yet to graduate from college, although we have been given many privileges of being able to be educated and we're well on our way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donnie Wahlberg"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Tell me about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Well, we'd spoke before and of course Donnie Wahlberg is my (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Well, what made these boys special enough to be able to make this miraculous achievement which is what many people see it as?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Well I don't think they -- I don't think they call themselves special.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What is your advice to other kids in that area and neighborhoods like that around America for avoiding the pitfalls of crime and violence and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Find hobbies to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "George, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Any play that goes on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "They are very capable of being typical teenagers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "This is only the second time you got on a plane in your lives was to come to the studio today, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "ORGAN: By the time you got back to your -- where your parents came from in Vietnam, what do you think your father would have made with the fact that you've been offered this place at Yale and you're at UMass?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "He would have been very proud of us.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Yale"], "LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "So George, I mean, do you think that he instilled in you the kind of values that you're clearly showing us tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "He definitely did, because I mean when I was in elementary school he would always check my homework, make sure I was doing well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What's your Twitter address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "It's billy_baker.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Emmett"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "The pair of you have been almost surrogate fathers, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I mean more so, Emmett, certainly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "What are you doing at UMass?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Studying chemical engineering.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "ORGAN: What do you want to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Chemical engineer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "What about you, what are you going to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Thinking about studying biomedical engineering.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What do you want to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Journalism.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "You'll be a journalist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Maybe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Just how cold is it getting out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "You know what for just for you, Piers, the temperature is exactly the same in Celsius as it is in Fahrenheit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}, "docId": "140106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "(inaudible) tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "All the way through until Friday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]